Full-Stack Software Engineer with over 2 years of industry experience. I excel in fast-paced environments, and always place myself in team leadership roles. My technical background is very versatile, and I enjoy learning new things on the spot. It keeps life interesting!

# **Employment History**

## **❖ Fidelity Investments – DevOps & Test Automation,** Westlake, TX

Associate Software Engineer, January 2016 – Present

#### DevOps

- Developed a migration strategy to move development teams and their code repositories from Subversion to Git
- Facilitated training sessions to teach basic source control concepts using Git, Stash, SourceTree, and different development workflows (Central Repository, Feature Branches, Gitflow)
- Onboarded new applications to a Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment pipeline, and modified existing CI/CD pipelines as needed
- Made improvements to an existing DevOps dashboard to showcase metrics such as code coverage, deployment metrics, application compliance, etc.

### **Test Automation**

- Worked in a development team to create and maintain a library of common test automation functions in Java
- Migrated Java applications from Ant to Maven, and moved artifacts out of source control repositories into artifact repositories (Nexus, Artifactory)
- Upgraded and configured Java/Spring projects as needed
- Converted manual test cases into automated functional and regression tests, and incorporated them into existing CI/CD pipelines

### **❖ Fidelity Investments – Leap Program,** Cary, NC

Associate Software Engineer, August 2015 – December 2015

- Completed Software Engineering training modules on Object-Oriented Analysis & Design, UNIX Essentials, Oracle
  11g & Data Modeling, Big Data, Java/XML, The Spring Framework, Service Oriented Architecture, Developing
  Dynamic Web Applications, and C# Programming
- Developed an automated system for Fidelity's Asset Management division to import, normalize, and store big data from credit rating agencies into a Hadoop environment. This allowed the firm to find credit rating mismatches between those original ratings and data imported from credit rating aggregation services, potentially saving the company millions of dollars in future liabilities

#### ❖ Fidelity Investments, Westlake, TX

Technical Intern, June 2014 – August 2014

- Constructed a single page web application to showcase project overviews and associated metrics
- Tested RESTful web services for security vulnerabilities, proper inputs/outputs, and overall responsiveness

### ❖ Ayoka Systems, Arlington, TX

Web Application Developer Intern, June 2013 - May 2014

- Designed and built web applications using the Grails framework and MVC architecture
- Modified existing applications based on customer needs, and performed testing to verify that product specifications have been met

# Education

# ❖ University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, May 2015

- Senior Design Project Leader, Team SmartGrass (September 2014 May 2015)
- College of Engineering Student Ambassador (January 2015 May 2015)
- Founding father of the Theta-Omega chapter of the Kappa Sigma Fraternity (November 2013 May 2015)